<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Syngenta</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="product1">Previous Product</string>
    <string name="product2">Next Product</string>
    <string name="button_submit">Submit</string>

    <string-array name="product_list">
        <item>Aatrex</item>
        <item>Atrazine</item>
        <item>Bicep II Magnum</item>
        <item>Bicep II Magnum FC</item>
        <item>Bicep Lite II Magnum</item>
        <item>Boundary</item>
        <item>Dual II Magnum</item>
        <item>Flexstar GT 3.5</item>
        <item>Halex GT</item>
        <item>Lexar EZ</item>
        <item>Lumax EZ</item>
        <item>Prefix</item>
        <item>Princep 4L</item>
        <item>Sequence</item>
        <item>Touchdown HiTech</item>
        <item>Touchdown Total</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_top_load">Top Load</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_product">Product</string>
    <string name="title_activity_launcher">Syngenta</string>


    <string name="title_section1">Products</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Top Load Matrix</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Bulk Sites</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_bulk_site">DisplayBulkSite</string>

    <string name="describeAatrex">AAtrex® 4L is the liquid formulation of this broad spectrum herbicide that provides season-long control of many broadleaf weeds and some grasses in corn, sorghum, sugarcane and other crops specified on the label. AAtrex 4L has outstanding application flexibility – it can be applied preplant surface, preplant incorporated, pre-emergence, or post-emergence. It is also serves as an excellent tank mix partner to enhance the control of certain broadleaf weeds and grasses.</string>
	<string name="describeAtrazine">Atrazine 4L is the liquid formulation of this broad spectrum herbicide that provides season-long control of many broadleaf weeds and some grasses in corn, sorghum, sugarcane and other crops specified on the label. Atrazine 4L has outstanding application flexibility – it can be applied preplant surface, preplant incorporated, pre-emergence, or post-emergence. It is also serves as an excellent tank mix partner to enhance the control of certain broadleaf weeds and grasses.</string>
	<string name="describeBicep">Strong on broadleaf weeds and grasses, gentle to the crop and proven to keep fields cleaner longer than the competition, Bicep II Magnum® herbicide is an excellent choice for foundation weed control in corn and sorghum crops. Bicep II Magnum is a powerful combination of S-metolachlor and atrazine, two active ingredients with years of proven performance on hard-to-control weeds, making it a stronger, longer, better chemistry for your crops. </string>
	<string name="describeBoundary">Boundary® 6.5 EC soil-applied herbicide delivers proven early-season grass and broadleaf weed control, excellent resistance management and rotation flexibility. By using Boundary, you can extend the post-application window up to five weeks after planting, thereby protecting your yield and keeping your fields cleaner longer. Boundary contains two modes of action and controls weeds that are resistant to glyphosate and ALS-inhibitors in potatoes and soybean.</string>
	<string name="describeDual">Dual II Magnum® herbicide is effective at eliminating early-season weed competition that threatens to reduce yields in corn, soybeans, cotton, potatoes, sorghum and a variety of other crops. It provides long-lasting control of most annual grasses and small-seeded broadleaf weeds while offering unsurpassed crop safety. It’s unbeatable application flexibility and ability to fit all cropping systems make it a versatile weed resistance and weed management tool.</string>
	<string name="describeFlexstar">Flexstar® GT 3.5 herbicide is specifically formulated to combat weeds in cotton and soybean that are difficult to control with glyphosate alone or are resistant to glyphosate and ALS-inhibitors.  It contains two leading active ingredients, glyphosate and fomesafen, delivering two different modes of action. Flexstar GT 3.5 also contains Isolink™ II Technology, a unique adjuvant system designed to optimize the systematic activity of glyphosate and the contact activity of fomesafen.</string>
	<string name="describeHalex">Halex® GT herbicide offers the best opportunity for one-pass, post-emergence broadleaf weed and grass control in glyphosate-tolerant corn (Agrisure® GT or Roundup Ready® hybrids). Halex GT is Glyphosate with Residual™ and provides a more convenient alternative to other post-emergence, straight glyphosate corn herbicide programs. By combining three modes of action in a one-pass system, Halex GT saves growers time and money and helps with managing resistant weeds.</string>
	<string name="describeLexar">Lexar® EZ herbicide maximizes yield in field corn, field seed corn, field silage corn, yellow popcorn, sweet corn and grain sorghum. Powered by Callisto Plant Technology®, the enhanced formulation delivers longer-lasting residual, greater application flexibility and broader-spectrum control than competitive herbicides. Lexar EZ combines three highly effective active ingredients to prevent early-season weed competition.</string>
	<string name="describeLumax">Lumax® EZ herbicide is a combination of three highly effective active ingredients used for control of annual grasses and broadleaf weeds in field corn, field seed corn, field silage corn, yellow popcorn, sweet corn and grain sorghum. Powered by Callisto Plant Technology®, Lumax EZ delivers unmatched broad-spectrum burndown plus residual weed control, application flexibility and crop safety. Lumax EZ maximizes yield potential by preventing early-season weed competition.</string>
	<string name="describePrefix">Prefix® residual herbicide offers the proven performance of fomesafen combined with S-metolachlor for superior control of broadleaf weeds and grass in cotton and soybean. By providing timely weed control using two unique modes of action, Prefix is an ideal solution for controlling glyphosate and ALS-resistant weeds, and its superior weed control helps to maintain clean fields and increase potential yield throughout the season.</string>
	<string name="describePrincep">Princep® 4L is a liquid herbicide that controls more than 40 broadleaf and annual grass weeds in fruits, nuts and corn (see label for specific crops). It’s long-lasting weed and grass protection is heightened by its excellent crop safety benefits and unbeatable tank mix flexibility. Princep 4L has many of the same benefits of atrazine but can be used in areas where atrazine is not allowed or desired. In addition, it also may be applied in Christmas tree plantings and shelterbelts.</string>
	<string name="describeSequence">Sequence® herbicide combines contact and residual activity for reliable weed control in many crops including cotton, soybean, peanut and sugarbeets. With two distinct modes of action, Sequence delivers weed resistance management benefits with effective knockdown control of existing weeds and residual control of troublesome weeds, such as pigweed, crabgrass and annual grass. With flexible application timing, Sequence is a time-saving tool for any producer\'s weed control program.</string>
	<string name="describeTouchdownTotal">Touchdown Total® from Syngenta is a glyphosate herbicide with a formulation that delivers unsurpassed weed control and excellent crop safety over the top of glyphosate-tolerant (GT) corn, soybeans, cotton, sugarbeets and many other crops. The highly concentrated formulation also makes handling, storage and application convenient and efficient. Touchdown Total is registered on 230 crops and delivers non-selective control of more than 170 weed species.</string>
	<string name="describeTouchdownHitech">Touchdown HiTech® from Syngenta is a glyphosate herbicide with a formulation that delivers unsurpassed weed control and excellent crop safety over the top of glyphosate-tolerant (GT) corn, soybeans, cotton, sugarbeets and many other crops. The highly concentrated formulation also makes handling, storage and application convenient and efficient. Touchdown HiTech is registered on 230 crops and delivers non-selective control of more than 170 weed species.</string>

</resources>
